35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe], circa 1972; 7 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas leaning against a stone wall], 13
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas sitting on a stone wall in front of a body of water (Cliffs of Moor?)], 14
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at table (dark photo)], 15
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at table], 16
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Horse and buggy], 17
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing on the back of a carriage], 18
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: City rooftops], 19
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: City rooftops], 20
  - Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe], circa 1972; 8 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: City rooftops], 1
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People dressed in costumes], 2
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Golden sign that says "Dromoland"], 3
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of a church], 4
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Man standing by a bar], 5
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas sitting in front of castle in Europe], 6
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas sitting in front of castle in Europe], 7
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: (Dark photo) People sitting at a table in front of a large window in a restaurant], 8
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: A city street], 9
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas sitting in a horse and buggy], 10
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Looking out car window, man walking behind cows], 11
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing near a castle in Europe], 12
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Construction work], 13
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Frances Ryan Thomas standing between a man amd a woman, mountains in the background], 14
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas on a bus], 15
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas at a long dining table], 16
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Person playing the harp], 17
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of a church (dark photo)], 18
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: (Dark photo) )Inside of a cathedral, large organ?], 19
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Dark photo], 20
  - Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe], circa 1972; 9 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: (Dark photo) Chandelier], 1
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: (Dark photo) Inside a cathedral], 2
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Restaurant tables], 3
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Looking out a car window, two level bus driving on the road], 4
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Road], 5
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Road], 6
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Road], 7
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: City street], 8
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: City], 9
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Stone building in Europe], 10
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Donkeys], 11
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: A green house], 12
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of a many windowed room], 13
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Travel magazines (Iceland)], 14
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: A set table in a restaurant], 15
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: A chandlier], 16
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of a building with the title "Calcina"], 17
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of a building with the title "Calcina"], 18
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing on a sidewalk], 19
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Four women holding coat of arms], 20
  - Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe], circa 1972; 10 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Woman standing by a lake, mountains in background], 1
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Horse-drawn carriage in front of a ruined building in Europe], 2
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: City], 3
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Horse and buggies, and cars parked on street], 4
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Ruined building in Europe], 5
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Large pillared building in Europe], 6
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People dressed in costumes], 7
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Large pillared building in Europe], 8
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People sitting in a horse and buggy], 9
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Man playing a guitar in a restaurant], 10
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Fountains], 11
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Large cathedral in Europe, (Notre Dame, Paris (?))], 12
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of a room with high, painted ceilings, (Versailles (?))], 13
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Fountains in Europe, (Garden at Versailles (?))], 14
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Large theatre, seating and chandeliers (Theatre in Versailles (?))], 15
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: A farm with horses], 16
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Mountains, horses grazing in Europe], 17
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: ? Bright, red light emerging from behind a mountain], 18
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: A rock formed in an arch], 19
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Man on rocky hillside], 20
  - Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe], circa 1972; 11 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Cows on a farm in Europe], 1
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Chapel to the left, unknown building at the right], 2
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People walking through snowy mountains], 3
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lake, mountains in background], 4
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People riding horses], 5
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of a factory], 6
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of a factory], 7
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Factory building], 8
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Model of river and mountain ranges (?)], 9
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of a control room], 10
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Golden statue of a bird], 11
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Globus Cruciger], 12
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Swords], 13
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Statue of an angel holding a bow and arrow], 14
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Shop that says "The Old (illegible) Shop"], 15
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Wall with a bearded man's face engraved in it], 16
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Side of a castle in Europe], 17
  - Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe], circa 1972; 12 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: The ruins of a Roman amphitheatre (Colloseum, Rome (?))], 1
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Canal in Venice, (Bridge of Sighs (?))], 2
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Canal in Venice], 3
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People riding in a gondola, (St. Marks Square in the Background)], 4
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People riding in a gondola, (St. Marks Square in the Background)], 5
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Horse statues], 6
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Sistine Chapel?, St. Marks Basilica (?)], 7
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Large bell], 8
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Large bell], 9
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Side of Sistine Chapel, St. Marks Basilica?], 10
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People riding in gondolas], 11
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People riding in a gondola], 12
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People riding in gondolas], 13
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: View of city in Italy (Venice)], 14
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Venice], 15
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: People riding in a horse-drawn carriage], 16
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Boat on water], 17
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Paper that reads "Emblems of Canada"], 18
  - Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico], circa late 1960s; 13 (Box 1586)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico] [: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 1
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 2
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: (Pan Am) Airplane on the runway], 3
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Aerial view of land], 4
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Statue of a man sitting], 5
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Flower garden in front of large building], 6
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Flower garden in front of large building], 7
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: City buildings], 8
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Building], 9
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: City], 10
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Aerial view of a city], 11
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Aerial view of land], 12
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Aerial view of land], 13
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Aerial view of land], 14
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Aerial view of land], 15
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Flowers], 16
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Observation tower], 17
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Statue of James Wolfe], 18
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Statue of a knight riding a horse], 19
  - Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico], circa late 1960s; 14 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Large building], 1
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Abstract statues of people], 2
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Abstract building], 3
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Flowers, Building], 4
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Sheep walking on the side of a road, mountains in the background], 5
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Building with snowy mountains in the background], 6
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Railroad tracks, mountains in the distance], 7
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Building with snowy mountains in the background], 8
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Archway with a sign that reads " [?] Lake House"], 9
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Train riding by, snowcapped mountain in the background], 10
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: River running by snowcapped mountains], 11
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: River running by snowcapped mountains], 12
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: River running by snowcapped mountains], 13
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: River running by mountains], 14
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Train tracks], 15
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Train track bridge over river], 16
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Sign that reads "Lapointe Pier"], 17
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Body of water surrounding a city], 18
  - Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico], circa late 1960s; 15 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: A city], 1
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Two level bus], 2
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: A building with a funnel-like roof], 3
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Building], 4
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: A map that says at the left hand corner "Historic Stanley Park"], 5
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: A light house], 6
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: A boat on water], 7
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: A park], 8
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: A park], 9
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Horse-drawn carriage for tours], 10
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Looking out from horse-drawn carriage at park], 11
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Looking out from horse-drawn carriage at a building], 12
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Tall structure], 13
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Large stone building with a copper dome top in Canada], 14
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Large stone building in Canada], 15
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Large stone building with a copper dome top in Canada], 16
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Large building lit up at night], 17
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Boats on water by mountains], 18
  - Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico], circa late 1960s; 16 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Inside of a building (airport?)], 1
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: View from an airplane], 2
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: View from an airplane], 3
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: An airport], 4
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: View from an airplane], 5
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: View from an airplane], 6
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Airplane on runway], 7
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Airplane flying over body of water], 8
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Trolley riding down a city street], 9
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Golden Gate Bridge], 10
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Trollies riding down a city street], 11
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: (Blurry photo)], 12
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Inside of a church], 13
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Sign that reads "Old St. Mary's Center"], 14
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: City street], 15
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: City street], 16
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Trolley riding down a city street], 17
  - Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico] [Items 1-3] Carousel number 18 [Items 4-17], circa late 1960s; 17 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Harbor], 1
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: City], 2
    - [Carousel number 17 [Canada; California; Mexico]: Trolley riding through city street], 3
    - Beginning of Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)] [: City buildings], 4
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Tour boat on water], 5
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Building with palm trees], 6
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Room with a chandelier], 7
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Cars driving on road], 8
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Driving on road], 9
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: View from an airplane], 10
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: View from an airplane], 11
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Driving by a harbor], 12
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: View from a car], 13
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Building that looks like a castle], 14
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Painting of a Woman (Royalty?)], 15
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Painting of a Woman (Royalty?)], 16
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Lowell Thomas leaning on a wall - The Armada Lounge], 17
  - Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)], circa 1972; 18 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Cliffs], 1
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: City], 2
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: City], 3
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Building], 4
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: City with mountains in the distance], 5
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Woman wearing a costume], 6
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: People riding in a row boat], 7
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Iceland flags], 8
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Busy city street], 9
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Large building with a dome top], 10
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Flower garden], 11
    - [Carousel number 18 [Iceland, England and Ireland (many commercially purchased slides)]: Portraits of people hanging on wall], 12
    - Beginning of Carousel number 19 [South America] [:Driving on road, sign that reads "Miami Beach"], 13
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Driving, city view at right], 14
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Driving, city view at right], 15
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Driving, cruise ship at right], 16
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Car], 17
  - Carousel number 19 [South America], circa 1972; 19 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Car radio], 1
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in chair], 2
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting together ], 3
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting together ], 4
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Lowell Thomas sitting in the cockpit of the plane], 5
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Lowell Thomas sitting in the cockpit of the plane], 6
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Airport], 7